<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<stringresources>
    <strings>

        <string id="PAUSED" index="7">
            <en>PAUSED</en>
            <es>PAUSA</es>
            <de>ANGEHALTEN</de>
            <it>PAUSA</it>
            <fr>PAUSE</fr>
            <ru>ПАУЗА</ru>
            <pt>PAUSADO</pt>
            <nl>PAUZEREN</nl>
            <no>PAUSET</no>
        </string>

        <string id="LEVEL">
            <en>LEVEL</en>
            <es>NIVEL</es>
            <de>LEVEL</de>
            <it>LIVELLO</it>
            <fr>NIVEAU</fr>
            <pt>NÍVEL</pt>
            <ru>УРОВЕНЬ</ru>
            <nl></nl>
            <no></no>
        </string>

        <string id="FISH_UNLOCKED">
            <en>NEW FISH UNLOCKED</en>
            <es>NUEVO PEZ DESBLOQUEADO</es>
            <de>NEUER FISCH FREIGESCHALTET</de>
            <it>NUOVO PESCE SBLOCCATO</it>
            <fr>NOUVEAU POISSON DÉVERROUILLÉ</fr>
            <ru>НОВАЯ РЫБА РАЗБЛОКИРОВАНА</ru>
            <pt>NOVO PEIXE DEBLOQUEADO</pt>
            <nl></nl>
            <no></no>
        </string>

        <string id="TAP_TO_PLAY">
            <en>TAP TO PLAY</en>
            <es>TOQUE PARA JUGAR</es>
            <de>BERÜHRE UM ZU SPIELEN</de>
            <it>TOCCA PER GIOCARE</it>
            <fr>APPUYEZ POUR JOUER</fr>
            <ru>Нажмите, чтобы играть</ru>
            <pt>TOQUE PARA JOGAR</pt>
            <nl>TRYCK FÖR ATT SPELA</nl>
            <no>Tapp for å spille</no>
        </string>

        <string id="INSTRUCTIONS_AIM">
            <en>Match 3 blocks or more to destroy the blocks and clear them from the game screen.\n\n Use power ups to clear more blocks or collect 3 rainbow blocks to make a random power up that you can use.\n\nManage to collect 3 fishes in their bubles and you win the level.</en>
            <es>Combina 3 bloques o más para destruirlos y eliminarlos de la pantalla de juego. Usa potenciadores para eliminar más bloques o consigue tres bloques arco iris, con los que obtendrás un potenciador al azar. Si consigues recoger 3 peces dentro de sus burbujas, superarás el nivel.</es>
            <de>Kombiniere 3 oder mehr Blöcke, um sie zu zerstören und vom Bildschirm zu entfernen. Verwende Power-ups, um mehr Blöcke zu entfernen, oder sammle 3 Regenbögen-Blöcke ein, um ein zufälliges Power-up zu erzeugen. Wenn du es schaffst, 3 Fische in ihren Blasen einzusammeln, gewinnst du den Level.</de>
            <it>Abbina 3 o più blocchi per distruggerli e rimuoverli dalla schermata di gioco. Usa i potenziamenti per eliminare più blocchi o raccogli 3 blocchi arcobaleno per ottenere un potenziamento casuale. Cattura 3 pesci nelle loro bolle e vincerai il livello.</it>
            <fr>Associez 3 blocs ou plus pour détruire les blocs et les retirer de l'écran. Utilisez des bonus pour retirer plus de blocs ou collectez 3 blocs arc-en-ciel pour créer un bonus aléatoire que vous pouvez utiliser. Si vous parvenez à collecter 3 poissons dans leurs bulles, vous terminez le niveau.</fr>
            <ru>Соединяйте 3 или более блоков, чтобы уничтожить блоки и очистить их c игрового поля. Используйте бонусы, чтобы очистить больше блоков и соберите 3 радужных блока, чтобы получить случайное усиление, которое вы сможете использовать. Попробуйте собрать 3 рыбки в их пузырьки, и вы выиграете уровень.</ru>
            <pt>Combine 3 blocos ou mais para destruir os blocos e limpá-los da tela do jogo. Use power-ups para limpar mais blocos ou colete 3 blocos arco-íris para criar um power up aleatório que você pode usar. Consiga coletar 3 peixes em suas bolhas e você ganha o nível.</pt>
            <nl></nl>
            <no></no>
        </string>

        <string id="COMPLETED">
            <en>COMPLETED</en>
            <es>COMPLETADO</es>
            <de>ABGESCHLOSSEN</de>
            <it>COMPLETATO</it>
            <fr>TERMINÉ</fr>
            <ru>ПРОЙДЕН</ru>
            <pt>CONCLUÍDO</pt>
            <nl></nl>
            <no></no>
        </string>

        <string id="VOID">
            <en></en>
            <es></es>
            <de></de>
            <it></it>
            <fr></fr>
            <ru></ru>
            <pt></pt>
            <nl></nl>
            <no></no>
        </string>

    </strings>
</stringresources>
